mainstreethost.com 2018-11-01

# Privacy Policy | Mainstreethost Digital Marketing Agency

**Mainstreethost Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy discloses how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.mainstreethost.com (the “Site”). It will notify you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the Site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

 **INFORMATION COLLECTION**

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

 **We collect Device Information using the following technologies:**

  * “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).
  * “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
  * “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
  * “Google Analytics”, “Google Adwords”, “Google Tag Manager” and “Microsoft Bing Ads” tracks user experience and performance/conversion rates.
  * “Hotjar”, “HubSpot” and “Mouseflow” tracks user experience and performance/conversion rates.
    * You can get more information about Hotjar by visiting the [‘about Hotjar’ section ](https://help.hotjar.com/hc/en-us/categories/115001323967-About-Hotjar)of our support site. Hotjar assists its users/customers in providing their end users with a better experience and service as well as assist them in diagnosing technical problems and analyzing user trends. Most importantly, through Hotjar’s services, the functionality of the Hotjar Enabled Site can be improved, making them more user-friendly, more valuable, and simpler to use for the end users.
    * You may opt-out from having Hotjar collect your information when visiting a Hotjar Enabled Site at any time by visiting our [Opt-out](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out)page and clicking ‘Disable Hotjar’ or enabling Do Not Track (DNT) in your browser.
  * Mouseflow is a website analytics tool that provides session replay, heatmaps, funnels, form analytics, feedback campaigns, and similar features/functionality.
    * Mouseflow may record your clicks, mouse movements, scrolling, form fills (keystrokes) in non-excluded fields, pages visited and content, time on site, browser, operating system, device type (desktop/tablet/phone), screen resolution, visitor type (first time/returning), referrer, anonymized IP address, location (city/country), language, and similar meta data. Mouseflow does not collect any information on pages where it is not installed, nor does it track or collect information outside your web browser.
    * If you’d like to opt-out, you can do so at <https://mouseflow.com/opt-out>.
    * If you’d like to obtain a copy of your data, make a correction, or have it erased, please contact us first or, as a secondary option, contact Mouseflow at [privacy@mouseflow.com](mailto:privacy@mouseflow.com).
    * For more information, see Mouseflow’s Privacy Policy at <http://mouseflow.com/privacy/>.
    * For more information on Mouseflow and GDPR, visit <https://mouseflow.com/gdpr/>.

 **PURCHASE INFORMATION**

We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you. When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain this information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

 **HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on the Site. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to fulfill an order placed through the Site. Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

  * Communicate with you;
  * Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and
  * When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

 **BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING**

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

 **You can opt out of targeted advertising by:**

FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads

GOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous

BING – https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:  http://optout.aboutads.info/.

 **SURVEYS AND CONTESTS**

From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests.  Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information.  Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level).  Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.  Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

 **DO NOT TRACK**

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

 **LINKS**

The Site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

 **DATA RETENTION**

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

 **SECURITY**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the Site, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

 **MODIFICATION**

From time-to-time we may change this Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, for any purpose, and without notice.  By utilizing this site, you are consenting to and acknowledging the terms of this Privacy Policy.

 **YOUR RIGHTS**

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

If you would like to exercise the rights detailed above, or have inquires related to your rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), please contact our Data Protection Officer (“DPO”) at:

ATTN: DPO  
207 Commerce Drive,  
Amherst, NY, 14228, United States

If you are a California Resident, California Code Section 1798.83 (known as the “Shine the Light” law), permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes.  To make such a request, please write to us at:

ATTN: CA Privacy Rights  
207 Commerce Drive,  
Amherst, NY, 14228, United States

 **CONTACT US**

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at marketing@mainstreethost.com or by mail using the details provided below:

207 Commerce Drive  
Amherst, NY, 14228  
United States
